Cameron HOCHBERG, Security Researcher

cam.hochberg@gmail.com 36 boulevard Foch 94170 - Le Perreux sur Marne +33 (0)6 21 20 58 76

Nationality: French

LinkedIn Website MS Thesis

Summary

I'm a Client-Side Developer with a passion for game development and security. I have worked on the MMORPG Dofus, mainly on the network layer of the game and its anti-bot security measures. I participate in CTF competitions and have won awards for best writeups.

Key Skills

C#, C++, Rust, Cryptography, PyTorch

Experience

Client-Side Developer — Ankama, Roubaix

September 2022 to present

- Helped with the migration of Dofus from AS3 to C# with Unity
- Reworked the network layer and implemented a new protocol using DotNetty and Protobuf
- Implemented obfuscation for both the game and network layer as anti-bot measure
- Audited the game for security concerns

Google CTF

July 2020 and July 2021

- Helped xtal team with cryptographic problems
- Exploited a lattice hidden in the challenge Story
- Exploited a nonce redundancy in AES GCM for the challenge Pythia
- Exploited a vulnerability in the prime generation algorithm for the Chunk Noris challenge

Al Research Assistant — Case Western Reserve University Computer and Data Science department Soumya Ray's research lab, Cleveland OH

September 2019 to December 2020

- Helped to create an environment to test the efficiency of AI assistants using Unity, OpenHaptics Plugin
- Created the Passive and Active AI assistants used during testing Conversion of the experience from 3D to 2D

Penetration Test Intern — Armature Technologie, Paris

May 2018 to July 2018

- Created a web app for pen testing report generation using Django
- · Organized the reports database
- Created an associated API for easier access to this database

Education

Bachelor & Master of Computer Science — Case Western Reserve University, Cleveland, Ohio (United States), May 2022

- Focus on Networking and Security
- Major Subjects: Computer Security, Internet Security & Privacy, Machine Learning, Advanced Game Design
- Wrote a master thesis on defending against Al Generative Adversarial Network attacks

Hacking Competitions

CryptoCTF 2022: 10/421 ALLES! CTF 2021: 24/523

BambooFox CTF 2021: 36/513 Tokyo Westerners CTF 6th 2020: 59/648

Union CTF 2021: 53/466 ALLES! CTF 2020: 48/470

Google CTF 2021: 62/379 (Best Writeup prize for Pythia) Google CTF 2020: 161/625 (Best Writeup prize for Chunk Norris)

Technical Skills

<u>Programming Languages</u>: C/C++, C#, Rust, Python, SQL, Java, PHP, HTML, Javascript, NodeJS, Unity HLSL <u>Technologies</u>: Git, Godot, Docker, Unix, Django, Sockets, PyTorch, TCP/UDP, DotNetty, Protobuf, IDA pro

Languages

French Mother Tongue

English Bilingual (TOEFL 116/120)

Spanish Intermediate

Japanese Fluent (JLPT 3)

Korean Beginner